Guide to the Lolo National Forest Collection 1894-1987
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana-Missoula
Lolo National Forest Collection
1894-1987
University of Montana, Mansfield Library, Archives and Special Collections The University of Montana—Missoula Missoula, MT 59812 406-243-2053 http://www.lib.umt.edu/asc library.archives@umontana.edu
Mss 774
5.5 linear feet of textual materials, 1.6 linear feet of maps and 351 images
The Lolo National Forest Collection contains materials related to the administration and history of Lolo National Forest, which is located in western Montana. The collection contains documents concerning the changing boundaries of the National Forest, the land management, and historical landmarks like the Ninemile Remount Station, as well as administrative files from the Missoula National Forest and Cabinet National Forest, both which contain lands transferred to Lolo. Finally the collection includes photographs, primarily of the Ninemile Remount Station and Civilian Conservation Corps activites conducted from the camp there during the 1930s and 1940s.
Historical Note
Lolo National Forest was established in 1906 and is located in western Montana along the Clark Fork River (formerly Missoula River) and St. Regis River. It extends to the Montana-Idaho border to the west, the Kootenai National Forest and Flathead Indian Reservation to the north, the Missoula Valley and Lewis and Clark National Forest to the east, and the Bitterroot National Forest to the south. Since its establishment, Lolo National Forest acquired land from Missoula National Forest, Cabinet National Forest, and Selway National Forest. The forest is currently located within Region 1 of the United States National Forest System (USFS) and spans over 2 million acres. The Lolo National Forest is divided into five ranger districts: Missoula, Plains/Thompson Falls, Ninemile, Seeley Lake, and Superior. The forest’s Supervisor’s Office is in Missoula. The National Forest has managed a range of activities over the years including lumbering and reforestation, grazing, settlement, recreation, preservation, and fire control.
This collection contains administrative files for Lolo National Forest, as well as administrative files accumulated from other forests absorbed into Lolo. These files include information related to boundaries, land use, and the history of the forest. The collection also contains work diaries, reports on game and campground improvements, maps created by the National Forest, materials related to the publication of Thirty-two Years in the Mule Business, a short work published by the National Forest about the Ninemile Remount Station, and a series of photographs of the Ninemile Remount Station and its operations, including the Civilian Conservation Corps activites of the 1930s and 1940s. The collection is arranged into six series: Administrative files, Diaries, Reports, Publications, Maps, and Photographs.
Please note that these records do not comprise a complete or representative unit of records produced by the Lolo National Forest over the years encompassed by the collection’s date range as the records were not acquired in a systematic manner. The archival records for Region 1 of the USFS are kept in the National Archives and Records Administration Pacific Alaska Region repository in Seattle, Washington and are listed there as Record Group 95.
The administrative files contain documents detailing the boundaries and management of Lolo National Forest. Included in these files are documents created by forests whose lands were absorbed into Lolo National Forest, specifically, Missoula National Forest and Cabinet National Forest. The series also contains a group of files documenting the history of the Forest and historic landmarks within the Forest. The diaries are comprised of the work diaries by former Forest employees working in the 1940s through the 1950s. The reports relate to campground improvement, winter game studies, timber marking and cutting, grazing permits and verification, road maintenance, and fire control. One report about campground improvement contains annotations by E.H. Myrick, former supervisor of Lolo National Forest.
The publications files consist of the research files and drafts used for Thirty-two Years in the Mule Business: The USDA/Forest Service Remount Depot and Winter Range, by Jane Reed Benson. The maps are “seen area” maps, which record the observations of a cartographer standing at a single point and drawing the full 360 degree panorama visible from that point. These maps center around specific lookout points within the forest and the patrol study field notes related to the mapped area. Many of the maps are hand drawn, others are printed maps upon which the surveyor has shaded specific regions of the map.
The photographs are of the Ninemile Remount Station and the animals (mules and horses) that were housed at the station as well as the CCC camp that existed there.
This collection consists of 6 series:
Series I: Administrative files, 1908-1979, 2.3 linear feet
Subseries 1: Lolo National Forest, 1909-1975, 0.7 linear feet
Subseries 2: Cabinet National Forest, 1909-1979, 0.9 linear feet
Subseries 3: Missoula National Forest, 1908-1938, 0.3 linear feet
Subseries 4: Kaniksu National Forest, 1964, 1 folder
Subseries 5: Kootenai National Forest, 1910 1 folder
Subseries 6: Landmarks and historical information, 1923-1976, 0.3 linear feet
Series II: Work diaries, 1946-1957, 2.5 linear feet
Series III: Reports: 1935-1937, 0.4 linear feet
Series IV: Publications 1924-1982 0.3 linear feet
Series V: Maps, 1931-1973, 1.6 linear feet
Series VI: Photographic materials, 1894-1987, 351 images
Researchers must use collection in accordance with the policies of Archives and Special Collections, the Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, and The University of Montana-Missoula.
Materials in this collection were acquired in six accessions dating from 1987-1992. The series of administrative files and the series of reports were donated by Milo McLeod. The M.B. Mendenhall diaries and series of maps was donated by Tom Reese.
Oral histories acquired with materials in Series IV: Publications and Series VI: Photographic Materials were moved upon acquisition to the Archives' oral history collection. These oral histories are filed under the designation OH 086 and consist of interviews conducted by Jane Reed Benson related to the Ninemile Remount Station.
Related materials include Forest Service Records, Record Group 95, National Archives and Records Administration Pacific Alaska Region, Seattle, WA and
Benson, Jane Reed, 1978. The U.S. Forest Service Remount Depot and Winter Range: Oral and Written History Prepared for a Government Agency. M.I.S. Thesis, The University of Montana.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Myrick, E. H.
Lolo National Forest (Agency: U.S.); Lolo National Forest (Agency: U.S.); Lolo National Forest (Agency: U.S.)--Officials and employees--Diaries; Ninemile Remount Station (Mont.); United States. Forest Service. Remount Depot.
Cabinet National Forest (Mont.); Lolo National Forest (Mont.); Lolo National Forest (Mont.)--History; Lolo National Forest (Mont.)--Maps; Lolo National Forest (Mont.)--Photographs; Missoula National Forest (Mont.); Ninemile Remount Depot (Mont.)
Camp sites, facilities, etc.--Montana--Lolo National Forest; Forest reserves--Montana; Game and game-birds--Montana--Lolo National Forest; Horses--Montana--Lolo National Forest; Mules--Montana--Lolo National Forest
Photographs
Forestry and Forestry Products; Montana; Maps
- Administrative files, 1908-1979; Series I; 2.3 linear feet
  This series consists of files detailing the establishment of Lolo National Forest, its boundaries, the acquisition of land resulting from the disbanding of other National Forests, the upkeep of forest infrastructure, and leases on use of the land by companies such as the Northern Pacific Railway. A portion of the administrative files consist of files inherited from now defunct National Forests that were incorporated into Lolo National Forest. These forests include Missoula National Forest and Cabinet National Forest.
  This series consists of six subseries: Lolo National Forest, Cabinet National Forest, Missoula National Forest, Kootenai National Forest, Kaniksu National Forest, and Landmarks and historical information.
  - Lolo National Forest, 1909-1978; Subseries 1; 0.7 linear feet
    This subseries contains files regarding the boundaries of the forest, its resources, and documents concerning land use and management.
    - Allotment estimates, 1916 (Box-folder 1/1)
    - Bicentennial cooperation, 1975 (Box-folder 1/2)
    - Boundaries - survey, 1909 (Box-folder 1/3)
    - Boundaries - additions and unit reports, circa 1921 (Box-folder 1/4-6)
    - Boundaries - section survey notes, 1924-1925 (Box-folder 1/7-8)
    - Boundaries - Public Domain Commission, 1930, 1934, 1935 (Box-folder 1/9)
    - Boundaries - Selway National Forest transfer, 1931-1934 (Box-folder 1/10)
    - Boundaries - Clearwater National Forest transfer, 1931-1934 (Box-folder 1/11)
    - Boundaries - boundary adjustment with Helena National Forest, 1934, 1939, 1940 (Box-folder 1/12)
    - Boundaries - miscellaneous, 1937, 1942, 1946 (Box-folder 1/13)
    - Contacts, 1956. 1969, 1972 (Box-folder 2/1)
    - Contacts - Kirkwood report, 1963 (Box-folder 2/2)
    - Fire control, 1943 (Box-folder 2/3)
    - Helena National Forest and Lewis and Clark National Forest boundaries, 1909 (Box-folder 2/4)
    - Land status, 1909-1927 (Box-folder 2/5)
    - Land values - Clark Fork, 1912 (Box-folder 2/6)
    - Land values - Thompson Falls, 1912 (Box-folder 2/7)
    - Leases - Anaconda Mining Company, 1930-1963 (Box-folder 2/8)
    - Leases - Northern Pacific Railway Company, 1947-1962 (Box-folder 2/9)
    - Recreation, 1927, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 2/10)
    - Settlement, 1926 (Box-folder 2/11)
    - Timber survey, 1909 (Box-folder 2/12)
    - Timber survey, 1909 (Box-folder 2/13)
  - Cabinet National Forest, 1909-1979; Subseries 2; 0.9 linear feet
    This subseries contains files regarding the boundaries of the forest, its management in terms of repairs and land use, its history, and a “last will and testament” describing the dissolution of the forest in 1954.
    - Boundaries - reports, 1909 (Box-folder 2/14-15)
    - Boundaries - examination, 1909-1912 (Box-folder 3/1-2)
    - Boundaries - additions, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 3/3)
    - Boundaries - additions, 1941, 1943 (Box-folder 3/4)
    - Boundaries - additions and eliminations, 1952-1954 (Box-folder 3/5)
    - Boundaries - additions and transfers, 1910-1923 (Box-folder 3/6)
    - Boundaries - Blackfoot addition, 1916-1924 (Box-folder 3/7)
    - Boundaries - Blackfoot addition, 1926 (Box-folder 3/8)
    - Boundaries - section survey notes, 1924-1925 (Box-folder 3/9)
    - Establishment of Cabinet National Park, 1916 (Box-folder 3/10)
    - Flood control - St. Regis River, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 3/11)
    - History and place names, 1908-1950 (Box-folder 3/12)
    - Historical information, 1937-1939 (Box-folder 4/1)
    - Land status, 1908-1936, bulk 1930-1936 (Box-folder 4/2-3)
    - Land status, 1913-1919 (Box-folder 4/4)
    - Land status, 1922-1929 (Box-folder 4/5)
    - Land status, 1947-1979 (Box-folder 4/6)
    - Land status, 1950 (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Land status, undated (Box-folder 4/8)
    - Last will and testament, undated (Box-folder 4/9)
    - Primitive areas, 1932 (Box-folder 4/10)
    - Roads - Paradise Cutoff, 1934-1940 (Box-folder 4/11)
    - Supervision, 1910-1912, 1925, 1928 (Box-folder 4/12)
  - Missoula National Forest, 1908-1938; Subseries 3; 0.3 linear feet
    This subseries contains files concerning the boundaries and history of the forest.
    - Boundaries - survey, 1909 (Box-folder 5/1-3)
    - Boundaries, 1909-1912, 1915, 1923 (Box-folder 5/4)
    - Boundaries, 1924-1927 (Box-folder 5/5)
    - Boundaries - Helena National Forest transfer, 1928-1929 (Box-folder 5/6)
    - Sales - Dobler brothers, 1920 (Box-folder 5/7)
    - Settlement, 1908, 1909, 1929 (Box-folder 5/8)
  - Kaniksu National Forest, 1964; Subseries 4; 1 folder
    This subseries contains information about recreation areas around Noxon Rapids Reservoir.
    - Recreation - Noxon Rapids Reservoir, 1964 (Box-folder 5/9)
  - Kootenai National Forest, 1910; Subseries 5; 1 folder
    This subseries contains a report about settlement within the National Forest.
    - Settlement, 1910 (Box-folder 5/10)
  - Landmarks and historical information, 1923-1976; Subseries 6; 0.3 linear feet
    This file contains files regarding the history of Lolo National Forest, landmarks and memorials within the forest, and general files on the history of the National Forest Service.
    - Ernest B. Clark memorial, 1923-1927 (Box-folder 5/11)
    - Correspondence and notes, 1973, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 5/12)
    - Fish Creek Tree, 1966-1969, 1975 (Box-folder 5/13)
    - Fish Creek Tree photographs, 1975 (Box-folder 6/1)
    - Jim Gerard memorial, 1953 (Box-folder 6/2)
    - Historical information, 1927-1971, 1979 (Box-folder 6/3)
    - Index to Early Days in the Forest Service, 1960, 1963, 1974, 1975 (Box-folder 6/4)
    - Indian Post Office, 1940, 1955 (Box-folder 6/5)
    - Inventory of historic places, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 6/6)
    - Names of National Forests, 1909 (Box-folder 6/7)
    - National Forest Service, 1954, 1968, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 6/8)
    - Nominations to National Register of Historic Places, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 6/9)
    - Origin of name Missoula, 1938 and undated (Box-folder 6/10)
    - State historic preservation plans, 1974 (Box-folder 6/11)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 6/12)
    - War Service Honor Roll correspondence and newsletters, 1942-1945 (Box-folder 6/13)
    - Worksheet for compiling honor roll, 1942-1945 (Box-folder 6/14)
- Work diaries, 1946-1957; Series II; 2.5 linear feet
  This series contains work diaries of various Lolo National Forest employees and is arranged in alphabetical order according to the name of employee.
  - Dale L. Arnold, June 13, 1955-July 7, 1955 (Box-folder 6/15)
  - Dale L. Arnold, July 8, 1955-July 31, 1955 (Box-folder 6/16)
  - Dale L. Arnold, August 1, 1955-August 30, 1955 (Box-folder 6/17)
  - Dale L. Arnold, September 29, 1955-October 29, 1955 (Box-folder 6/18)
  - Dale L. Arnold, October 30, 1955-November 19, 1955 (Box-folder 6/19)
  - Dale L. Arnold, November 20, 1955-December 16, 1955 (Box-folder 6/20)
  - Dale L. Arnold, December 18, 1955-January 14, 1956 (Box-folder 6/21)
  - Dale L. Arnold, January 15, 1956-February 15, 1956 (Box-folder 6/22)
  - Dale L. Arnold, February 16, 1956-March 17, 1956 (Box-folder 6/23)
  - Dale L. Arnold, March 18, 1956-April 17, 1956 (Box-folder 7/1)
  - Dale L. Arnold, April 18, 1956-May 16, 1956 (Box-folder 7/2)
  - Dale L. Arnold, May 17, 1956-June 14, 1956 (Box-folder 7/3)
  - Dale L. Arnold, June 15, 1956-July 14, 1956 (Box-folder 7/4)
  - Dale L. Arnold, August 12, 1956-September 8, 1956 (Box-folder 7/5)
  - Dale L. Arnold, September 9, 1956-October 6, 1956 (Box-folder 7/6)
  - R. J. Beaubier, January 1, 1950-May 28, 1950 (Box-folder 7/7)
  - R. J. Beaubier, May 28, 1950-June 24, 1950 (Box-folder 7/8)
  - R. J. Beaubier, June 25, 1950-July 22, 1950 (Box-folder 7/9)
  - R. J. Beaubier, July 23, 1950-August 19, 1950 (Box-folder 7/10)
  - R. J. Beaubier, August 20, 1950-September 16, 1950 (Box-folder 7/11)
  - R. J. Beaubier, September 17, 1950-October 14, 1950 (Box-folder 7/12)
  - R. J. Beaubier, October 15, 1950-November 11, 1950 (Box-folder 7/13)
  - R. J. Beaubier, November 12, 1950-December 9, 1950 (Box-folder 7/14)
  - R. J. Beaubier, December 10, 1950-January 6, 1951 (Box-folder 7/15)
  - R. J. Beaubier, January 7, 1951-February 3, 1951 (Box-folder 7/16)
  - R. J. Beaubier, February 4, 1951-March 3, 1951 (Box-folder 7/17)
  - R. J. Beaubier, March 4, 1951-March 4, 1951 (Box-folder 7/18)
  - R. J. Beaubier, April 1, 1951-December 31, 1951 (Box-folder 7/19)
  - R. J. Beaubier, January 1, 1952-June 30, 1952 (Box-folder 7/20)
  - R. J. Beaubier, July 1, 1952-December 31, 1952 (Box-folder 8/1)
  - R. J. Beaubier, January 1, 1953-December 31, 1953 (Box-folder 8/2)
  - R. J. Beaubier, January 1, 1954-December 31, 1953 (Box-folder 8/3)
  - R. J. Beaubier, January 1, 1955-June 17, 1955 (Box-folder 8/4)
  - Robert A. Cook, April 13, 1952-May 10, 1952 (Box-folder 8/5)
  - Robert A. Cook, May 12, 1952-June 7, 1952 (Box-folder 8/6)
  - Robert A. Cook, June 8, 1952-July 5, 1952 (Box-folder 8/7)
  - Robert A. Cook, July 7, 1952-August 3, 1952 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Robert A. Cook, August 5, 1952-September 12, 1952 (Box-folder 8/9)
  - Robert A. Cook, September 13, 1952-October 20, 1952 (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Robert A. Cook, October 21, 1952-December 2, 1952 (Box-folder 9/2)
  - Robert A. Cook, December 3, 1952-January 17, 1953 (Box-folder 9/3)
  - Robert A. Cook, January 19, 1953-February 27, 1953 (Box-folder 9/4)
  - Robert A. Cook, February 28, 1953-April 10, 1953 (Box-folder 9/5)
  - Robert A. Cook, April 11, 1953-May 22, 1953 (Box-folder 9/6)
  - Robert A. Cook, May 23, 1953-July 6, 1953 (Box-folder 9/7)
  - Robert A. Cook, July 7, 1953-August 13, 1953 (Box-folder 9/8)
  - Robert A. Cook, August 12, 1953-September 17, 1953 (Box-folder 9/9)
  - Robert A. Cook, September 17, 1953-October 16, 1953 (Box-folder 9/10)
  - Robert A. Cook, October 17, 1953-November 22, 1953 (Box-folder 9/11)
  - Robert A. Cook, November 23, 1953-December 18, 1953 (Box-folder 9/12)
  - Robert A. Cook, December 19, 1953-January 17, 1954 (Box-folder 9/13)
  - Robert A. Cook, January 18, 1954-February 13, 1954 (Box-folder 9/14)
  - Robert A. Cook, February 14, 1954-March 12, 1954 (Box-folder 9/15)
  - Robert A. Cook, March 13, 1954-April 10, 1954 (Box-folder 9/16)
  - Robert A. Cook, April 11, 1954-May 7, 1954 (Box-folder 9/17)
  - Robert T. Dale, July 9, 1954-August 16, 1954 (Box-folder 9/18)
  - Robert T. Dale, August 17, 1954-August 25, 1954 (Box-folder 9/19)
  - Howard L. Gorsuch, May 9, 1954-June 5, 1954 (Box-folder 9/20)
  - Howard L. Gorsuch, June 6, 1954-July 3, 1954 (Box-folder 9/21)
  - Howard L. Gorsuch, July 4, 1954-July 13, 1954 (Box-folder 9/22)
  - Howard L. Gorsuch, August 1, 1954-August 28, 1954 (Box-folder 9/23)
  - Howard L. Gorsuch, August 29, 1954-September 25, 1954 (Box-folder 9/24)
  - Howard L. Gorsuch, September 26, 1954-Octoeber 23, 1954 (Box-folder 9/25)
  - Howard L. Gorsuch, October 24, 1954-November 20, 1954 (Box-folder 9/26)
  - Howard L. Gorsuch, November 21, 1954-December 18, 1954 (Box-folder 9/27)
  - Howard L. Gorsuch, December 19, 1954-January 15, 1955 (Box-folder 9/28)
  - Howard L. Gorsuch, January 16, 1955-Febrary 12, 1955 (Box-folder 9/29)
  - Howard L. Gorsuch, February 13, 1955-March 12, 1955 (Box-folder 9/30)
  - Howard L. Gorsuch, March 13, 1955-April 9, 1955 (Box-folder 9/31)
  - Howard L. Gorsuch, April 10, 1955-May 7, 1955 (Box-folder 9/32)
  - Howard L. Gorsuch, May 8, 1955-June 4, 1955 (Box-folder 10/1)
  - Howard L. Gorsuch, June 6, 1955-July 2, 1955 (Box-folder 10/2)
  - Howard L. Gorsuch, July 3, 1955-July 30, 1955 (Box-folder 10/3)
  - Howard L. Gorsuch, July 31, 1955-August 27, 1955 (Box-folder 10/4)
  - Howard L. Gorsuch, August 28, 1955-September 24, 1955 (Box-folder 10/5)
  - Howard L. Gorsuch, September 25, 1955-October 22, 1955 (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Howard L. Gorsuch, October 23, 1955-November 19, 1955 (Box-folder 10/7)
  - Howard L. Gorsuch, November 20, 1955-December 17, 1955 (Box-folder 10/8)
  - Howard L. Gorsuch, December 18, 1955-January 14, 1956 (Box-folder 10/9)
  - Charles P. Kern, March 26, 1951-April 25, 1951 (Box-folder 10/10)
  - Charles P. Kern, April 26, 1951-May 1, 1951 (Box-folder 10/11)
  - M.B. Mendenhall, June, August-October 1946 (Box-folder 18/1)
  - M.B. Mendenhall, November 1946, February-April 1947 (Box-folder 18/2)
  - M.B. Mendenhall, May-August 1947 (Box-folder 18/3)
  - M.B. Mendenhall, September-December 1947 (Box-folder 18/4)
  - M.B. Mendenhall, January-April 1948 (Box-folder 18/5)
  - M.B. Mendenhall, May-August 1948 (Box-folder 18/6)
  - M.B. Mendenhall, September-December 1948 (Box-folder 18/7)
  - M.B. Mendenhall, January-April 1949 (Box-folder 18/8)
  - M.B. Mendenhall, May-August 1949 (Box-folder 18/9)
  - M.B. Mendenhall, September-December 1949 (Box-folder 18/10)
  - M.B. Mendenhall, January-April 1950 (Box-folder 18/11)
  - M.B. Mendenhall, May-August 1950 (Box-folder 18/12)
  - M.B. Mendenhall, September-December 1950 (Box-folder 18/13)
  - M.B. Mendenhall, January-March 1951 (Box-folder 18/14)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, January 17, 1954-February 13, 1954 (Box-folder 10/12)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, February 14, 1954-March 13, 1954 (Box-folder 10/13)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, March 14, 1954-April 10, 1954 (Box-folder 10/14)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, April 11, 1954-May 8, 1954 (Box-folder 10/15)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, May 9, 1954-June 5, 1954 (Box-folder 10/16)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, June 6, 1954-July 3, 1954 (Box-folder 10/17)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, July 4, 1954-July 31, 1954 (Box-folder 10/18)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, August 1, 1954-August 28, 1954 (Box-folder 10/19)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, August 29, 1954-September 25, 1954 (Box-folder 10/20)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, September 26, 1954-Octoeber 23, 1954 (Box-folder 10/21)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, October 24, 1954-November 20, 1954 (Box-folder 10/22)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, November 21, 1954-December 18, 1954 (Box-folder 10/23)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, December 19, 1954-January 15, 1955 (Box-folder 10/24)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, January 16, 1955-Febrary 12, 1955 (Box-folder 10/25)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, February 13, 1955-March 12, 1955 (Box-folder 10/26)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, March 13, 1955-April 9, 1955 (Box-folder 10/27)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, April 10, 1955-May 7, 1955 (Box-folder 10/28)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, May 8, 1955-June 4, 1955 (Box-folder 10/29)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, June 5, 1955-July 2, 1955 (Box-folder 10/30)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, July 3, 1955-July 30, 1955 (Box-folder 10/31)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, July 31, 1955-August 27, 1955 (Box-folder 11/1)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, August 28, 1955-September 24, 1955 (Box-folder 11/2)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, September 25, 1955-October 22, 1955 (Box-folder 11/3)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, October 23, 1955-November 19, 1955 (Box-folder 11/4)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, November 20, 1955-December 17, 1955 (Box-folder 11/5)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, December 18, 1955-January 14, 1956 (Box-folder 11/6)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, January 15, 1956-February 11, 1956 (Box-folder 11/7)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, February 12, 1956-March 10, 1956 (Box-folder 11/8)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, March 11, 1956-April 7, 1956 (Box-folder 11/9)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, April 8, 1956-May 5, 1956 (Box-folder 11/10)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, May 6, 1956-June 2, 1956 (Box-folder 11/11)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, June 3, 1956-June 30, 1956 (Box-folder 11/12)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, July 1, 1956-July 28, 1956 (Box-folder 11/13)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, July 29, 1956-August 25, 1956 (Box-folder 11/14)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, August 26, 1956-September 22, 1956 (Box-folder 11/15)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, September 23, 1956-october 20, 1956 (Box-folder 11/16)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, October 21, 1956-November 17, 1956 (Box-folder 11/17)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, November 18, 1956-December 15, 1956 (Box-folder 11/18)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, December 16, 1956-January 12, 1957 (Box-folder 11/19)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, January 13, 1957-February 10, 1957 (Box-folder 11/20)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, February 10, 1957-March 10, 1957 (Box-folder 11/21)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, March 10, 1957-April 7, 1957 (Box-folder 11/22)